[### Live Map](https://piratemc.com/map/ "View the live map")Take a gander at the Pirate map to find out where you are!
    
    * * *
    
    * [Survival Live Map
        
        The main Survival Server, you'll probily want this one!
        
        ](https://piratemc.com/map/)
    
    * [Creative Live Map
        
        Build on our creative, you can use ships here too!
        
        ](https://piratemc.com/map/creative/)
    
    * [PvP Play Server
        
        PirateCraft PvP Practise!
        
        ](https://piratemc.com/map/pvp/)

    [### Guides](https://piratemc.com/guides/ "Visit the guide index")Learn to use the custom features on PirateCraft.
    
    * * *

    [### Information](https://piratemc.com/information/ "View the information index")Detailed information, gallery, videos, PirateCraft team and other detailed information about PirateCraft.
    
    * * *

    [### Pirate Codex](https://piratemc.com/pirate/ "Visit the Pirate Codex")Seek the pirate profile you are looking for!
    
    * * *
    
    * [Pirate Codex
        
        See a list of the pirates last online, or search for someone!](https://piratemc.com/pirate/)
    
    * [Top Monthly Voters
        
        She whos leading this month in votes!](https://piratemc.com/codex/topvoters/)

    [### Support Tickets](https://piratemc.com/support/ "Visit the forum index")Create a support ticket to contact the staff team!
    
    * * *
    
    [### Discord](https://discord.piratemc.com/ "Visit the forum index")Talk to staff and community on our discord
    
    * * *
    
    [### Community Forums](https://piratemc.com/forums/ "Visit the forum index")Chat on our message boards with the community!
    
    * * *

    * Report players
    * Report duplication or server crashing exploits
    * Request rollback of grief
    * Contribution Issue

    * Live annoucements, changelogs & events
    * Giveaways
    * Community & Staff support
    * Live gamechat
    * Crew channels & gamechat
    * Creator Channels
    * Voice chat

* Login / Register
    
    ### Login
    
    Already signed up? Log in!
    
    * Login useing the account you created
    * Or Login using your Google account

    ### Register
    
    Why Register to the the website?
    
    * Join our active Forums, be part of the community.
    * Create a private crew group and forum.
    * Get notified of updates.
    * Private Message players and Staff
    * View and interact with the activity feed

* Play now

##### Play PirateCraft now!

×

  Your browser does not support the video tag. Please use an newer browser.

Copy our server address **mc.piratemc.com** into your server list and play!

Close

1. [Home](https://piratemc.com/)
2. Privacy Policy & Terms Of Service

Privacy Policy & Terms Of Service
=================================

* * *

By playing on PirateCraft and using the piratemc.com website you are agreeing to play by the [server rules](https://piratemc.com/information/), You agree to the Privacy Policy and you agree to the Terms and Conditions of the Terms Of Service.

Privacy Policy
--------------

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our website.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: Username, e-mail address, password (Which is Encrypted), Date of Birth (Not required) and Sex (Not required).  The Name usually isn’t ever a personal name, but an anonymous alias for your characters username. We also record your IP address when you register to help verify you are not a bot. We don’t require any personal information to register.  
You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

#### Store payments are handed by Third party’s

We do not store any of the personal information entered when purchasing digital items though our store, all of this information is handed by third parties.

Our store page redirects to the Buycraft service that acts as a store front and processes  payments through either PayPal or Stripe.

Buycraft have developed their own system for players to have their own accounts, for players to exercise their data rights under GDPR, Requests should be directed to BuyCraft as the data controller so they can educate the player how how to maage their data though the Tebex Accounts system, BuyCrafts Notice on GDPR can be found [here](https://help.buycraft.net/article/215-gdpr-and-your-buycraft-account).

If you use Paypal to process a payment [here is their GDPR Page](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/gdpr-readiness-requirements?CampaignName=VanityURL-GDPR).

If you use Stripe to process a payment [here is their GDPR page](https://stripe.com/guides/general-data-protection-regulation).

We do not store any information related to payments through the store, That is all handed by the third parties listed above.

#### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

#### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

* To personalize your experience  
    (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
* To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
* To send periodic emails
* The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions, it will not be sold or used by third parties.

### Where do we keep this information?

This information is saved in our MySQL database for our website, all password are encrypted and never listed as plain text.

### Visiting the website

When someone visits [https://piratemc.com](https://piratemc.com/) we use a third party service; Google Analytics to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behavior patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website. You can find more information on how cookies are used on this website in the Cookies Policy below.

If we do want to collect personally identifiable information through our website, we will be up front about this. We will make it clear when we collect personal information and will explain what we intend to do with it.

### Links to Other Web Sites

This privacy notice does not cover the links within this site linking to other websites. Those sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy, and if you have questions about how a site uses your information, you’ll need to check that site’s privacy statement.

### Access/Deleting to Your Personal Information

You are entitled to access the personal information that we hold, We do not store any personal information past what you entered at registration on piratemc.com which you already have access too! If you would like a copy please log in and visit your profile page, it is all available to you.

If you wish for your data on piratemc.com to be deleted please contact us on our [team page](https://piratemc.com/information/team/).

### Cookies

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes.

#### What are cookies?

Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to your personal computer, mobile or other device when you visit a website. Cookies are then sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognises that cookie. Cookies are useful because they allow a website to recognise a user’s device.

#### How long are cookies stored for?

_Persistent cookies_ – these cookies remain on a user’s device for the period of time specified in the cookie. They are activated each time that the user visits the website that created that particular cookie.

_Session cookies_ – these cookies allow website operators to link the actions of a user during a browser session. A browser session starts when a user opens the browser window and finishes when they close the browser window. Session cookies are created temporarily. Once you close the browser, all session cookies are deleted.

Cookies do lots of different jobs, like letting you navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, and generally improve the user experience.

You can find more information about cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and [www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

#### Cookies used on the Website

A list of all the cookies used on the Website by category is set out below.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

##### Strictly necessary cookies

These cookies enable services you have specifically asked for.  These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the Website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the Website.

##### Performance cookies

These cookies collect anonymous information on the pages visited.  By using the Website, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device.

These cookies collect information about how visitors use the Website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how the Website works.

##### Functionality cookies

These cookies remember choices you make to improve your experience.  By using the Website, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device.

These cookies allow the Website to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personal features. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customise. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.

##### Third party cookies

These cookies allow third parties to track the success of their application or customise the application for you. Because of how cookies work we cannot access these cookies, nor can the third parties access the data in cookies used on our site.

For example, if you choose to ‘share’ content through Twitter or other social networks you might be sent cookies from these websites. We don’t control the setting of these cookies, so please check those websites for more information about their cookies and how to manage them.

### Embedded content from other websites

pages on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

We use Google Analytics, Google have developed their own [Opt-out tool](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) to opt-out of Google Analytics.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or send an email notifying you of any changes.

Terms and Conditions
--------------------

By donating to PirateCraft/piratemc.com you are stating that:

1. You are over the age of 18 OR have parental permission
2. You have authorization to use the debit/credit card and/or paypal account
3. You will not chargeback, dispute, reverse any payments
4. You will not abuse your gifts and/or ranks
5. We reserve the right to ban any account without notice for any reason.
6. You agree to everything listed above and below. NO REFUNDS WILL BE GRANTED

1) We reserve the right to change, with or without notice, any rank price that has been set forth. We also reserve the right to change the contents of a specific rank – the benefits of a certain rank can change, and you will not be entitled to the old rank benefits if we change it. Rest assured that no rank benefit, or any other item in the store, will be changed without a valid, server-balancing reason.

2) You agree to indemnify the staff, owners, hosts, advertisers, officers, directors, employees, partners, and all other parties related to this servers staff. By agreeing to these terms, you agree not to present any lawsuit or other legal challenge against the server staff for any reason, whether related to your purchase or not.

3) You understand and agree that your use of this website and any services or content provided is made available and provided to you at your own risk. It is provided to you as-is and we expressly disclaim all warranties of any kind, expressed or implied, including but not limited to the warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, and non-infringement. You understand and agree that neither us nor any participant in the service provides professional advice of any kind and thus use of such advice or any other information is solely at your own risk and without our liability of any kind. Some jurisdictions may not allow disclaimers of implied warranties and the above disclaimer may not apply to you only as it relates to implied warranties.

4) You expressly understand and agree that we shall not be liable for any direct, indirect, special, incidental, consequential or exemplary damages, including but not limited to, damages for loss of profits, goodwill, use, data or other intangible loss (even if we have been advised of the possibility of such damages), resulting from or arising out of

(I) The use of or the inability to use the service, (II) The cost to obtain substitute goods and/or services resulting from any transaction entered into on through the service, (III) Unauthorized access to or alteration of your data transmissions, (IV) Statements or conduct of any third party on the service, or (V) any other matter relating to the service. Note that by accepting the terms in the document, you are also waiving your right, to take any action, legal or otherwise, against anyone or anything related to the staff, management, administrators, members, owners or any hosts of this server. You furthermore acknowledge that if any part of this document is found to be invalid or unenforceable in any way, any parts not found to be invalid or unenforceable will be considered fully valid and binding.

5) Any staff, owners, hosts, advertisers, officers, directors, employees, partners, and all other parties related to this servers staff reserve the right, with the appropriate permissions, to forcibly make you leave the server, permanently or temporarily, with no chance of refund – however this will never be unwarranted, this will only happen in the case of extreme rule-breaking. If you obey the rules, you will never be banned, plain and simple.

6) All terms and conditions are in effect indefinitely as soon as the contract is accepted, and will remain to be active even after you quit, are banished, removed, or if you leave the server/website/forum in any way.

Refund Policy: All sales are final, you may not buyback, stop, credit the server by any means necessary in order to receive your funds back that of which have been paid. And in doing so we reserve the right to disallow your continued play on the server/website/forums and not allow further funds to be added or taken away. We reserve the right to pursue any legal or collection action necessary to recover damages in the event of a forced charge-back.

### /50 Online

Sort Rank

##### Vote

Get daily vote key rewards for voting! Use your keys at `/warp cove`

Join the PirateCraft Discord server! [discord.piratemc.com](https://discord.piratemc.com/)

#### About Us

Piratecraft is a pirate themed minecraft server run by Pirates! Yarr! You can play right now IP: mc.piratemc.com You will need a [Premium JAVA Minecraft PC/Mac/Linux](https://www.minecraft.net/en-us/download/) to play on PirateCraft, you can get a game code from here.

Disclaimer: We are not affiliated or associated in any official way with [Mojang](https://mojang.com/).

#### Support

Need help? Open a Ticket!

#### Follow us

PirateCraft on social media

Copyright © PirateCraft 2012-2024. All rights reserved.

Insert/edit link
================

Close

Enter the destination URL

URL 

Link Text 

 Open link in a new tab

Or link to existing content

Search 

_No search term specified. Showing recent items._ _Search or use up and down arrow keys to select an item._

Cancel
